<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Podcast on EnterpriseReady</title>
    <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Podcast on EnterpriseReady</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Delivering Software That Enterprises Love with Chef’s Adam Jacob</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/01-adam-jacob-chef/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/01-adam-jacob-chef/</guid>
      <description>In this episode Grant interviews Adam Jacob, founder and CTO of Chef. Adam has been building Chef for over 10 years and during that time he has learned a LOT about how to deliver software that enterprises love. He has an incredible perspective and we were so glad to have him as one of our first guests.
Adam Jacob is co-founder and CTO of Chef, formerly known as Opscode, a configuration management tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Early Days of GitHub with Tom Preston-Werner</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/02-tom-preston-werner-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/02-tom-preston-werner-github/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we interview Tom Preston-Werner, founder and former CEO of GitHub. We mainly focus on Tom’s time at GitHub, where he built and scaled one of the most important developer tool companies in the world. However, many might not realize that Github is also one of the most successful enterprise software companies of the modern era. With over half of their revenue coming from large enterprise deals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product-Market Fit with Segment’s Peter Reinhardt</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/03-peter-reinhardt-segment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/03-peter-reinhardt-segment/</guid>
      <description>In episode 3 of EnterpriseReady, Grant chats with Peter Reinhardt, co-founder and CEO of Segment, to discuss how finding and maintaining product-market fit helped grow his enterprise-facing company.
About the Guest Peter Reinhardt is the CEO and founder of Segment, a Customer Data Infrastructure platform for businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source with CoreOS’s Alex Polvi</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/04-alex-polvi-coreos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/04-alex-polvi-coreos/</guid>
      <description>In episode 4 of EnterpriseReady, Grant chats with Alex Polvi, co-founder and CEO of CoreOS, which was recently acquired by Red Hat, to dive into detail about the nuances of building and selling an enterprise product that has an open source core.
About the Guest Alex Polvi is the Co-founder and CEO of CoreOS, which was recently acquired by Red Hat. Alex got his start in open source when he was in college which led him to doing infrastructure at Mozilla and eventually starting his first company, Cloudkick.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edith Harbaugh of LanchDarkley</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/05-edith-harbaugh-launchdarkley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/05-edith-harbaugh-launchdarkley/</guid>
      <description>Today we are talking with Edith Harbaugh, the CEO and Co-founder of LaunchDarkly, one of the first “feature flags as a service companies” where they offer a feature management platform aiming to help teams build better software. We’ll get some backstory on how she got into enterprise software and some of the lessons she learned building advanced enterprise features, including an elaborate Role Based Access Control system that ultimately missed the mark on simplicity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Peterson of Signal Sciences</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/06-andrew-peterson-signal-sciences/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/06-andrew-peterson-signal-sciences/</guid>
      <description>This episode I’m joined by Andrew Peterson, CEO and Co-founder of Signal Sciences an application security company building a nextgen WAF that is deployed throughout the Fortune 500. Before starting Signal Sciences, Andrew and his two co-founders built up scar tissue solving security problems at Etsy, a company known for pioneering many of the devops practices that are common today. This experience gave the unique insights and connections helped to shape their top-down go-to-market approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul Querna of ScaleFT</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/07-paul-querna-scaleft/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/07-paul-querna-scaleft/</guid>
      <description>In this episode of EnterpriseReady we are speaking with Paul Querna, the CTO and Cofounder of ScaleFT, which was acquired by Okta not too long ago. Paul likes to say that ScaleFT is in the business of granting people and machines access to the systems and endpoints they should be reaching. We get some back story on the company’s founding and then we focus on the Zero Trust concepts that ScaleFT evangelized that have their roots in a white paper published by Google that defined a new model for enterprise security, called BeyondCorp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dave Cole of Tenable</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/08-dave-cole-tenable/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/08-dave-cole-tenable/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to the EnterpriseReady Podcast! Today our guest is Davle Cole, who at the time of recording was the Chief Product Officer at Tenable, but has recently left to start a stealthy startup in the security space. This episode is long, but that’s because Dave has such a great history of bringing enterprise software to market and there were so many topics for us to dig into. Dave shares his 18 years of experience building world class products in the security space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zack Blum of Fleetsmith</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/09-zach-blum-fleetsmith/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/09-zach-blum-fleetsmith/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to the EnterpriseReady podcast, today our guest is Zack Blum, Founder and CEO of Fleetsmith. In the episode we dive into the founding story behind Fleetsmith and then move into how they brought the product to market. Given the nature of the business, the story of Fleetsmith is intertwined with lessons about what all companies should be doing for internal security. We also spend a good bit of time discussing how they’ve implemented user management by leveraging GSuite &amp;amp; Office365, as well as their approach to product assortment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joel Wallenstrom of Wickr</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/10-joel-wallenstrom-wickr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/10-joel-wallenstrom-wickr/</guid>
      <description>In this episode of the EnterpriseReady podcast, we sit down Joel W. CEO of Wickr, a secure messaging and communications platform. We learn a bit about Joel’s background in the cyber security industry, with a focus on his time running 3rd party security firms. From there, we dive into the history of Wickr, which started as a consumer, mobile first communications tool on the back of perfect forward secrecy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bob Tinker of MobileIron</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/11-bob-tinker-mobileiron/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/11-bob-tinker-mobileiron/</guid>
      <description>In this episode of the EnterpriseReady podcast, I sit down with Bob Tinker, co-founder of MobileIron, a company that he served as CEO of, from founding through IPO before stepping down in 2016. Bob recently co-authored a book called Survival to Thrival, in which he lays out the foundations for building and growing an enterprise software company. We focus on several of the frameworks that Bob developed for building a go-to-market playbook, including how to determine your best go to market approach, and how to continuously evolve your company in a fast-changing market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>William Morgan of Buoyant</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/12-william-morgan-buoyant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/12-william-morgan-buoyant/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to the EnterpriseReady podcast. Today we are talking with William Morgan, CEO, and Founder of Buoyant, a company that primarily focuses on contributing to the open-source ServiceMesh project, Linkerd. Linkerd was born out of William and his co-founder Oliver’s experience building infrastructure at Twitter, where they were responsible for reducing the frequency in which the infamous “Fail whale” surfaced. The opening portion of the episode gives us a unique look into how Twitter eventually scaled their platform with cloud-native technologies and how one of those patterns ultimately became the inspiration for Linkerd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rahul Vohra of Superhuman</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/13-rahul-vohra-superhuman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/13-rahul-vohra-superhuman/</guid>
      <description>In this episode of the EnterpriseReady podcast we sit down with Rahul Vohra, founder and CEO of Superhuman. Superhuman recently announced a $33m series B from A16Z which was their first funding announcement despite having raised over $17m previously. I have Rahul give us some details about his fundraising history and strategy which is quite unique. Rahul and I spend a lot of time discussing his experience of building software to solve problems that individuals encounter in the day-to-day work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Pryor of Trello</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/14-michael-pryor-trello/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/14-michael-pryor-trello/</guid>
      <description>In this episode of the entepriseready podcast, we hear from Michael Pryor the founder and CEO of Trello. Micheal has had an incredible career as one of the founders of FogCreek Software which has spun out products such as FogBugz, StackOverflow, Glitch and of course, Trello which was acquired by Atlassian for $425 million dollars back in 2017. We cover a wide range of topics primarily from the perspective of a bottom-up go-to-market approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Williams of Contrast Security</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/15-jeff-williams-contrast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/15-jeff-williams-contrast/</guid>
      <description>In this episode of the EnterpriseReady Podcast we interview Jeff Williams, founder and CTO of ContrastSecurity. We explore Jeff’s early career in cyber security where he worked as a security consultant as the internet started to gain early traction. From there, we dive into his founding role at a security consulting firm where he stayed very involved with the security community through his role as Global Chair of OWASP where he helped create the OWASP Top 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spence Green of Lilt</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/16-spence-green-lilt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/16-spence-green-lilt/</guid>
      <description>In episode 16 of EnterpriseReady, Grant speaks with Spence Green, Founder and CEO of Lilt. They discuss language translation services for enterprises and governments, the rigor required to deliver enterprise software, and the internationalization of products.
About the Guest Spence Green is the Founder and CEO of Lilt, a machine-assisted language translation company. He graduated from Stanford with a PhD in computer science and has published papers on machine translation, language parsing, and mixed-initiative systems and given talks on translator productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ben Hindman of Splash</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/17-ben-hindman-splash/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/17-ben-hindman-splash/</guid>
      <description>In episode 17 of EnterpriseReady, Grant joins Ben Hindman, Co-Founder &amp;amp; CEO of Splash. They discuss Ben’s path into enterprise software, the community-driven power of events, and the freemium business model.
About the Guest Ben Hindman is the Co-Founder &amp;amp; CEO of Splash, the world’s first event marketing software. He was previously National Events Manager at Thrillist in New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elizabeth Zalman of strongDM</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/18-elizabeth-zalman-strongdm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/18-elizabeth-zalman-strongdm/</guid>
      <description>In episode 18 of EnterpriseReady, Grant is joined by Elizabeth Zalman, Founder &amp;amp; CEO of strongDM. They discuss enterprise software go-to-market, remote teams, product prioritization frameworks, and SOC 2 certification.
Elizabeth Zalman is the Co-Founder &amp;amp; CEO of strongDM. Previously she was Co-Founder and CEO of the cross-device profile company Media Armor. After its acquisition, she served as VP of Analytics at the acquirer, Nomi. With over 15 years of experience leading data-driven organizations, she is an expert in analytics, data privacy, and security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>API Integrations with Mark Geene of Cloud Elements</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/19-mark-geene-cloud-elements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/19-mark-geene-cloud-elements/</guid>
      <description>In episode 19 of EnterpriseReady, Grant speaks with Mark Geene, CEO and Co-Founder of Cloud Elements. They discuss Mark’s early days in enterprise, integrations between apps and APIs, and the go-to-market lessons learned along the way.
About the Guest Mark Geene is the CEO and Co-Founder of Cloud Elements, a cloud API integration service. He was previously Vice President of [TenFold}(https://www.tenfold.com/), and held the same title at Oracle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Executive Visibility with Yvonne Wassenaar, CEO of Puppet</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/20-yvonne-wassenaar-puppet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/20-yvonne-wassenaar-puppet/</guid>
      <description>In episode 20 of EnterpriseReady, Grant is joined by Yvonne Wassenaar, CEO of Puppet. They discuss her experience serving on boards of enterprise software companies, transitioning from a single product company to multiple products, and the role of professional services.
Yvonne Wassenaar is a seasoned C-level executive with broad experience scaling, diversifying, and transforming businesses throughout the Americas, Europe, and Asia. She is currently the CEO of Puppet, and an advisor at Snyk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Product and Narrative with Michel Feaster of Usermind</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/21-michel-feaster-usermind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/21-michel-feaster-usermind/</guid>
      <description>In episode 21 of EnterpriseReady, Grant interviews Michel Feaster, CEO and Co-Founder of Usermind. They discuss Michel’s journey from gas station employee to enterprise software CEO, as well as the relationship between product, product marketing, and marketing.
Michel Feaster is the Co-Founder and CEO of Usermind, responsible for company vision, strategic direction, planning and execution. Michel’s enterprise software career spans almost 20 years with roles in sales, products, strategic marketing and general management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data-Driven Enterprise with Derek Steer of Mode</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/22-derek-steer-mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/22-derek-steer-mode/</guid>
      <description>In episode 22 of EnterpriseReady, Grant chats with Derek Steer, CEO of Mode. Together they pull back the curtain on data science tools, and how enterprise software companies can use data analysis to drive business forward.
Derek Steer is the CEO of Mode, a data analytics and business intelligence tool. Derek previously held analytics positions at numerous renowned companies including Yammer, Facebook, and Microsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Infrastructure with Abby Kearns of Cloud Foundry Foundation</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/23-abby-kearns-cloud-foundry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/23-abby-kearns-cloud-foundry/</guid>
      <description>In episode 23 of EnterpriseReady, Grant is joined by Abby Kearns, executive director of Cloud Foundry. They discuss enterprise infrastructure, the future of the cloud, technological ecosystems in China, and open source business models.
Abby Kearns is the Executive Director at Cloud Foundry Foundation. She’s had an immense technology career spanning operations, product marketing, product management and consulting at a mix of Fortune 500 and startup companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise Analytics with John Whaley of UnifyID</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/24-john-whaley-unifyid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/24-john-whaley-unifyid/</guid>
      <description>In episode 24 of EnterpriseReady, Grant joins John Whaley of UnifyID to discuss the process of monetizing university research, how technology enables businesses, and how inherent human behavior threatens security.
About the Guest John Whaley is the Founder and CEO of UnifyID, an identity platform based on implicit authentication. He previous founded Moka5, and was taught Program Analysis and Optimization as a lecturer at Stanford University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Stack Orchestration with Jonathan Ellis of DataStax</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/25-jonathan-ellis-datastax/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/25-jonathan-ellis-datastax/</guid>
      <description>In episode 25 of EnterpriseReady, Grant speaks with Jonathan Ellis of DataStax about Apache Cassandra and the complexity of distributed storage systems, as well as recruiting, interviewing, and hiring executives and engineers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Creation with Alex Miller</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/26-alex-miller-stackoverflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/26-alex-miller-stackoverflow/</guid>
      <description>In episode 26 of EnterpriseReady, Grant is joined by Alex Miller, former GM at Stack Overflow. They discuss Alex’s background, what Stack Overflow Enterprise does, Alex’s four constituencies of enterprise software, and much more.
About the Guest Alex Miller is the former General Manager of Stack Overflow, where he previously held the titles of Vice President of Operations and Chief of Staff. He was previously a concert and event producer, behind TechCrunch50, Open Angel Forum, and This Week in Startups, among others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Intelligence with Christian Beedgen of Sumo Logic</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/27-christian-beedgen-sumo-logic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/27-christian-beedgen-sumo-logic/</guid>
      <description>In episode 27 of EnterpriseReady, Grant speaks with Christian Beedgen, CTO &amp;amp; Co-Founder of Sumo Logic. They discuss Christian’s background, security analytics, the challenges faced by first generation on-prem software companies, and the evolving security landscape.
Christian Beedgen is the CTO &amp;amp; Co-Founder of Sumo Logic, a secure, cloud-native, machine data analytics service. He was previously Chief Architect at ArcSight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intentionality First with Enterprise Advisor Adam Gross</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/28-adam-gross-heroku/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/28-adam-gross-heroku/</guid>
      <description>In episode 28 of EnterpriseReady, Grant speaks with Adam Gross, seasoned enterprise investor and advisor. They discuss the inevitability of platform change, how software deployment has evolved, and how the enterprise application ecosystem might develop in years to come.
Adam Gross is an enterprise investor and advisor. He was previously the CEO of Heroku, SVP of Marketing and Sales at Dropbox, and VP of Platform and Developer Marketing at Salesforce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Achieving Ubiquity with Mitchell Hashimoto of HashiCorp</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/29-mitchell-hashimoto-hashicorp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/29-mitchell-hashimoto-hashicorp/</guid>
      <description>In episode 29 of EnterpriseReady, Grant speaks with Mitchell Hashimoto of HashiCorp. They discuss Hashicorp’s founding story, fundraising tactics and pricing models, and monetizing open source projects.
Mitchell Hashimoto is the founder and CTO of HashiCorp. He also created Vagrant, Packer, Serf, Consul, Terraform, Vault, and Nomad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On-Call Management with Alex Solomon of PagerDuty</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/30-alex-solomon-pagerduty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/30-alex-solomon-pagerduty/</guid>
      <description>In episode 30 of EnterpriseReady, Grant speaks with Alex Solomon of PagerDuty. They dive deep into product assortment, incident response management, on-call alerting, and company culture insights.
Alex Solomon is the CTO and Co-Founder of PagerDuty. Prior to PagerDuty, he was a software development engineer at Amazon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monoliths and Microservices with Rob Zuber of CircleCI</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/31-rob-zuber-circle-ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/31-rob-zuber-circle-ci/</guid>
      <description>In episode 31 of EnterpriseReady, Grant speaks with Rob Zuber, CTO at CircleCI. They discuss Rob’s expansive range of disciplines and the perspectives he’s gained on topics like fundraising, hiring, mentoring, scaling, and delivering value to customers.
About the Guest Rob Zuber is a startup expert and the CTO of CircleCI. He previously co-founded Distiller, Copious, and YooHoot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Gregoire of Brighton Park Capital</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/32-mike-gregoire-brighton-park-capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/32-mike-gregoire-brighton-park-capital/</guid>
      <description>In episode 32 of EnterpriseReady, Grant speaks with Mike Gregoire of Brighton Park Capital. They discuss strategies for growing through a recession, the changing role of modern enterprise salespeople, and the internal metrics Mike uses when evaluating acquisitions.
About the guest Mike Gregoire is a Partner at Brighton Park Capital and is a member of the Investment Committee. Previously, Mike was the Chairman and CEO of CA Technologies and Chairman and CEO of Taleo Corporation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shishir Mehrotra of Coda</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/33-shishir-mehrotra-coda/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/33-shishir-mehrotra-coda/</guid>
      <description>In episode 33 of EnterpriseReady, Grant is joined by Shishir Mehrotra of Coda. They discuss important lessons for building and launching products, as well as Shishir’s role as a technology leader at YouTube in it’s pivotal early years, just after the Google acquisition.
About the guest Shishir Mehrotra is the Co-Founder and CEO of Coda, a cloud-based document editor. He was previously the Director of Product Management at YouTube, and in years prior, Shishir was the Director of Program Management at Microsoft.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gene Kim of Tripwire</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/34-gene-kim-tripwire/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/34-gene-kim-tripwire/</guid>
      <description>In this episode, Grant interviews Gene Kim, Co-founder and former CTO of Tripwire. A giant in the world of DevOps, Kim is the author of the successful books, The Unicorn Project (2019), The Phoenix Project (2013), and The DevOps Handbook (2016). Listen as Gene and Grant discuss how enterprise organizations should structure their internal development priorities, the rise of the DevOps ecosystem, and why software engineers shouldn’t be railroaded into learning complex systems like Kubernetes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karthik Ranganathan of Yugabyte</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/35-karthik-ranganathan-yugabyte/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/35-karthik-ranganathan-yugabyte/</guid>
      <description>In episode 35 of EnterpriseReady, Grant speaks with Karthik Ranganathan of Yugabyte. They discuss Karthik’s enterprise journey, the fruits of maintaining a customer-driven ethos in business, and building modern databases. All this, and much more, are discussed in our latest episode of the EnterpriseReady Podcast.
About the Guest Karthik Ranganathan is the Founder &amp;amp; CTO of Yugabyte, the company behind the open source YugabyteDB, a high-performance distributed SQL database for global, internet-scale applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shannon Williams of SUSE</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/36-shannon-williams-suse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/podcast/36-shannon-williams-suse/</guid>
      <description>In episode 36 of EnterpriseReady, Grant speaks with Shannon Williams of SUSE. They unpack Shannon’s many years working with cloud-native and open source communities, his pioneering of Infrastructure as a Service, and the future of open source.
About the Guest With over 20 years of experience working in startups, Shannon Williams is currently Chief Revenue Officer of SUSE. He is also a governing board member at the CNCF, and previously co-founded Rancher Labs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
