<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GDPR Table of Contents on EnterpriseReady</title>
    <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GDPR Table of Contents on EnterpriseReady</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A guide to reading the full-text GDPR</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/how-to-read-gdpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/how-to-read-gdpr/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR of the TL;DR
  The official full text PDF of the GDPR is a 261 page beast. However, as we describe below, for SaaS companies who want to understand how this regulation impacts their product, they should read the 34 page abridged version of the GDPR we&amp;rsquo;ve compiled.
 Approaching the GDPR There has been a lot of advice written about how companies, developers and the technology industry, in general, should approach GDPR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GDPR 202: Controllers, processors and subjects’ rights</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/gdpr-202/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/gdpr-202/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps you’ve read our introduction to GDPR for SaaS companies and decided you want to learn more, or perhaps you’ve already been thinking about GDPR but haven’t spent a lot of time analyzing what it might mean for your company. Here, we try to take things a little deeper, looking at some of the core concepts of GDPR compliance and how they might apply to SaaS companies, specifically.
Because there’s still much ambiguity in terms of exactly how certain aspects will be defined and adjudicated in practice, there are places where we present more questions than we do answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How GDPR might affect the SaaS industry</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/gdpr-saas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/gdpr-saas/</guid>
      <description>Beyond the additional technical, contractual and ethical changes required to comply with GDPR (for more info, see our introduction to GDPR and our explanation of some key concepts), it’s unclear exactly how the sweeping new European Union will play out in practice. For example, on the most foundational level, nobody is quite sure how strictly certain requirements will be enforced, or how harsh the actual penalties will be.
However, it seems plausible that one of the unintended consequences of GDPR could be a contraction in the market for SaaS in the EU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How SaaS providers are preparing for GDPR</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/preparing-for-gdpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/preparing-for-gdpr/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes the best way to get a sense of something—especially something as complex as GDPR—is to see how your peers are thinking about it. Here’s a collection of documents that some of the most-successful cloud and SaaS providers have put together to explain how they plan to comply with the law; the requirements they have in place for customers and subprocessors; and also their lists of subprocessors that handle personal data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other useful GDPR links</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/useful-gdpr-links/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/useful-gdpr-links/</guid>
      <description>We’re not the only people reading, writing and thinking about GDPR. Aside from our collection of SaaS-company GDPR policies and documentation, here is a collection of links to other places where you’ll find some insightful discussion on the forthcoming law.
European Commission FAQ
A Stripe guide to the European privacy and data protection changes (Stripe):
Hacker news posts on GDPR
GDPR: Data subjects, controllers and processors, oh my! (Twilio)
Countdown to GDPR (Workday)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is GDPR and why should I care?</title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/what-is-gdpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/what-is-gdpr/</guid>
      <description>The European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) takes effect on May 25, 2018, and is rife with provisions that will impact the way in which SaaS vendors and their customers interact with each other. While it might be a big win for private citizens seeking some sovereignty over their personal information, it will undoubtedly make life at least a little trickier for every company doing business in the EU, employing EU citizens, handling the personal data of European citizens or doing business with companies who do business in the EU.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/gdpr-abridged/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.enterpriseready.io/gdpr/gdpr-abridged/</guid>
      <description>EnterpriseReady.io - GDPR Text for SaaS Companies (Abridged)  CHAPTER I General provisions
Article 1 Subject-matter and objectives
 This Regulation lays down rules relating to the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and rules relating to the free movement of personal data. This Regulation protects fundamental rights and freedoms of natural persons and in particular their right to the protection of personal data. The free movement of personal data within the Union shall be neither restricted nor prohibited for reasons connected with the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
